[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "How much do you charge?",
		"answer": "Price range is $139 to $399, based on the square footage of your home."
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "What is your hourly rate?",
		"answer": "Hourly rate is $69 per hour, two people. We recommend you to buy a package (Deep Clean, Standard clean, etc. for a flat rate, it is a better deal) Hourly rate is used when the time allotted run out and we did not finish your home and need one or more hours to finish it. It is also used when you need a partial job, not the whole house (just the bathrooms, or just the kitchen, etc.). In this case we charge you $149 for the first two hours, then $69 each additional. Hourly rate is also used to calculate Janitorial estimates and it depends on the square footage of the building and the number of days needed.  Hourly rate is also used to calculate domestic services. Here the cost is $39 per hour for one maid, $69 per hour for two maids, minimum of 4 hours a day, as many days per week as needed."
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "How can I book a service?",
		"answer": "You can book your service 24/7 on this link https://www.ourmaids.com/Book-Online You can call or text us 213-800-7644 from 7:am to 7:pm your time zone 7 days a week to book your service. "
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "Can I cancel any time?",
		"answer": "Yes, but at least a day (12 hours) before. click on this link https://www.ourmaids.com/reschedule-a-service to cancel or reschedule your service at any time. "
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "How long does it take to finish my home?",
		"answer": "It all depends on the size of it. If it is less than 1,000 s.f. they should be able to finish it in two hours."
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "How many people come to clean?",
		"answer": "Usually teams of two. Sometimes a solo team comes to your home. It also depends on the work load that day."
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": " What is your refund policy?",
		"answer": "We will refund your money immediately if you purchased a service and we cannot clean your home the scheduled day and time, unless we both agree on another date and time. PLEASE NOTE: We will not refund any money once the service is started."
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "Is your service guaranteed?",
		"answer": "Yes, contact us within 24 hours if you are not satisfied with the service. We will redo the areas in conflict at no extra cost to you."
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "Do you service my area?",
		"answer": "We service many cities in the United States, Canada and Mexico. If you found us on Google, we do service your area for sure. Here are some areas: Los Angeles county and all cities within and around it and Antelope Valley; Dallas-Fort Worth metroplex; Austin metro area; Winston-Salem-Greensboro metro area, Dover and surrounding areas, etc."
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "How long have you been in business?",
		"answer": "23 years. We started Our Maids, Inc. in Richardson, Texas in July 4, 2,000."
	},

	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "Are you insured?",
		"answer": "Yes, we carry insurance for your peace of mind, and ours."
	},

	{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "Are you Licensed?",
		"answer": "No. As of now, no one state requires a license to clean homes or offices."
	},

	{
		"id": 13,
		"question": "What is your policy about pets?",
		"answer": "We treat them with respect and do not deny service to anyone who has pets in their homes. We only ask to keep them away from the cleaners when they are at your home."
	},

	{
		"id": 14,
		"question": "How do you handle the key or code when we will not be home?",
		"answer": "We ask you to leave the key in a safe place so we can get it, open and leave it back when finish. If it is a code, please send it to your CustomerCare representative via text or email."
	},

	{
		"id": 15,
		"question": "Is our personal information safe with your company?",
		"answer": "Yes. Confidentiality is of utmost importance within Our Maids, Inc. We comply with United States law as well as State Law when it is different form U.S. law, and also with International law regarding the treatment of personal information. See Our privacy policy here https://www.ourmaids.com/privacy-policy."
	},

	{
		"id": 16,
		"question": "Do I have to pay before the service or after it is done?",
		"answer": "If you are a recurrent customer in good standing, you can pay after they finish. When ordering the first time, we ask you to pay before the team starts cleaning."
	},

	{
		"id": 17,
		"question": "Do I have to purchase the service every time?",
		"answer": "Yes, Please. But, there are other options. You can sign up for weekly, biweekly and monthly subscriptions and prepay as many times as you want. You can also sign up to a subscription were we can charge your card every month for the services performed."
	},

	{
		"id": 18,
		"question": "Do you work on weekends?",
		"answer": "Yes, we work Monday to Sunday from 7:am to 7:pm."
	},

	{
		"id": 19,
		"question": "Do you bring your own cleaning supplies and equipment?",
		"answer": "Yes, we do. But we can use yours if you want us to."
	},

	{
		"id": 20,
		"question": "What is the difference between a Deep Clean and a Standard Clean?",
		"answer": "With the Deep cleaning you get included: The oven, windows inside, cabinetry inside, fridge inside. With the Standard package, these items are not included."
	},

	{
		"id": 21,
		"question": "What forms of payments do you accept?",
		"answer": "We take all kinds of payments but cryptocurrency now. We prefer you pay your service on our online store with any kind of card. You can also pay with cash or check or send payments via Zelle, Cash App and Apple Pay."
	},

	{
		"id": 22,
		"question": "Can we request the team what we need cleaned?",
		"answer": "Yes, you can. However, please keep in mind that we offer different packages at different prices. They have a checklist for each one of them. If what you ask is not on their checklist, it will likely be an extra cost. Check our services here https://www.ourmaids.com/store"
	},

	{
		"id": 23,
		"question": "My dogs and cats poop all over my balcony. Do you clean this?",
		"answer": "Sorry, we do not do this kind of cleaning."
	},

	{
		"id": 24,
		"question": "Do you do office and clinic cleaning, janitorial services?",
		"answer": "Yes, we do janitorial services to all kinds of buildings."
	},

	{
		"id": 25,
		"question": "Do I have to sign a contract for Janitorial Services or Office Building cleaning and maintenance?",
		"answer": "You do not have to. The industry rule is to sign a one-year contract so it is a binding obligation. But we are the exception. If you keep paying your invoices, we keep cleaning your places. It's that simple."
	},

	{
		"id": 26,
		"question": "Do you do window cleaning?",
		"answer": "Yes, we do. Interior window cleaning is included with any deep cleaning package. Exterior window cleaning is done on the first floor only."
	},
	{
		"id": 27,
		"question": "OUR TYPES OF SERVICES & PRICES.",
		"answer": "Deep Cleaning"
	}
]
